<resources>
    <string name="question_1">If you could get a free trip, where would you go now and why?</string>
    <string name="question_2">If you could not work in any intellectual field, what non-intellectual job would you choose?</string>
    <string name="question_3">What physical accomplishment are you most proud of?</string>
    <string name="question_4">If you were to work in academia in the future, what position would you hold?</string>
    <string name="question_5">What do you consider to be your worst human trait?</string>
    <string name="question_6">What is a movie/series that is very popular but you have not seen? Why?</string>
    <string name="question_7">Which film is a must-see for you?</string>
    <string name="question_8">What hobby do you wish you had more time for?</string>
    <string name="question_9">Which family member are you closest to?</string>
    <string name="question_10">If you could have one superpower, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="question_11">What languages do you speak and want to learn?</string>
    <string name="question_12">What rule do you break often?</string>
    <string name="question_13">If you could live in any historical era, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="question_14">If you could live in the world of a fantasy novel, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="question_15">Would you like to be famous? How?</string>
    <string name="question_16">What would you consider to be a "perfect" weekday?</string>
    <string name="question_17">Tell me three things that you and your partner seem to have in common!</string>
    <string name="question_18">What are you most grateful for in life?</string>
    <string name="question_19">If you could change one thing about the way you were raised, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="question_20">Tell your partner the story of your life in four minutes, in as much detail as you can!</string>
    <string name="question_21">If you could learn the truth about yourself, your life, your future or anything else you'd like to know from a crystal ball</string>
    <string name="question_22">Is there something you've been dreaming of doing for a long time? Why haven't you done it yet?</string>
    <string name="question_23">What is the greatest achievement of your life?</string>
    <string name="question_24">What is the greatest value to you in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="question_25">What is your best memory of this summer?</string>
    <string name="question_26">If you knew now that you were going to die in a year, would you change anything in your life? Why?</string>
    <string name="question_27">What does friendship mean to you?</string>
    <string name="question_28">What role do love and emotions play in your life?</string>
    <string name="question_29">How close and intimate is your relationship with your family? Do you think you had a happier childhood than most people?</string>
    <string name="question_30">Complete the sentence "I wish I had someone to share..."!</string>
    <string name="question_31">If you were to become a close friend of your partner, tell me what they would need to know about you!</string>
    <string name="question_32">When was the last time someone saw you cry? And when was the last time you cried alone?</string>
    <string name="question_33">What is something so serious that it shouldn't be made fun of, if there are such things?</string>
    <string name="question_34">Your house is on fire and all your possessions in it. You've already rescued your loved ones and pets, but the only thing you can rush back to do is rescue them. What is it? Why?</string>
    <string name="question_35">How old would you be if you could choose your age now?</string>
    <string name="question_36">What would you do with the rest of your life if you didn't have to work now?</string>
    <string name="question_37">What did you want to be ten years ago? How close is this to your current profession?</string>
    <string name="question_38">If you could do whatever you wanted for a year, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="question_39">Do you have a secret talent for something, like singing?</string>
    <string name="question_40">If you could choose your own first name, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="question_41">What was the bravest thing you ever did?</string>
    <string name="question_42">What bad qualities did you inherit from your parents?</string>
    <string name="question_43">What was the best advice you ever got?</string>
    <string name="question_44">What do you want to achieve in the future?</string>
    <string name="question_45">What would you never want to give up in your life?</string>
    <string name="question_46">What type of people do you like?</string>
    <string name="question_47">What subjects or topics are you not comfortable with (why?)</string>?
    <string name="question_48">What kind of music do you like?</string>
    <string name="question_49">Do you have a motto, a story that has stuck with you, that you try to live by, act by?</string>
    <string name="question_50">What is one thing you would change in the country? Politics, other...?</string>
    <string name="question_51">How would you rob a bank?</string>
    <string name="question_52">Give me a guess what a cheesecake in a hat looks like</string>.
    <string name="question_53">Would you rather fight a duck the size of a horse, or a horse the size of 100 ducks?</string>
    <string name="question_54">How would you start a cult?</string>
    <string name="question_55">How many close friends do you have?</string>
    <string name="question_56">Do you go on holiday with your friends or with your family?</string>
    <string name="question_57">Why did you choose university over an OKJ course?</string>
    <string name="question_58">Would you like to move abroad? If so, where?</string>
    <string name="question_59">What is the next thing you would like to achieve in your life?</string>
    <string name="question_60">Where would you like to be in five years?</string>
    <string name="question_61">What do you think makes a friendship work?</string>
    <string name="question_62">What is important to you in a friendship?</string>
    <string name="question_63">What's the best productivity tip you've ever heard?</string>
    <string name="question_64">Do you procrastinate, if so why?</string>
    <string name="question_65">Is there a hobby/project you've wanted to do for a long time but haven't?</string>
    <string name="question_66">What languages do you speak, what do you like about them?</string>
    <string name="question_67">Do you use AI for work or hobbies?</string>

</resources>